Guide to the Terence Sellers Papers 1967-2000 MSS.167
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Writing, 154635
  - Subseries A: Short Stories, Poetry and Plays, 154872
    - "Poetry Roughs", 1970s; 154884 (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - "Princess Perfect: A Play" pages 1-25, undated; 154876 (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - "Princess Perfect: A Play" pages 26-50, undated; 154875 (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - "Princess Perfect: A Play" pages 51-66, undated; 154874 (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - "Princess Perfect", rough drafts, 1986; 154873 (Box 5, Folder 160 A)
    - "Psychological Survey of Clients" for article in Glamour Magazine (unpublished), 1986; 154907 (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - "Rhythms and Other Fragments", 1973; 154883 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - "The Real Duncan", 1980/1993; 154906 (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - "The Real Duncan", undated; 154905 (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - "Reluctantly Betrothed to Stan", 1988; 154904 (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - "Roads Poorly Taken", 1982; 154903 (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - "Sacher-Masoch Letter" and "To Achieve Death", 1989; 154902 (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - "Salo: 120 Days of Sodom", 1977; 154901 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - "Shit on Heroin" drafts (Original title: "Still life with Dilaudid"), undated; 156608 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - "Shit on Heroin: The $200", published in Bomb, 1980s; 156609 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - "Shoe Fetish As Expressed by a Dog", 1982; 154900 (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - "Stories '86", 1986; 154899 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - "Stories '86" continued, 1986-87; 154898 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - "A Subjective Analysis of Sexuality in Respect to Prostitution", 1980; 154897 (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - "The Tarot" for High Times and East West Journal, 1979; 156630 (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - "Tarot of the Moderns", 1979; 154896 (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - "Teenage Writing Left From the Fire", 1967-1970; 154895 (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - "Thanksgiving Day With Uncle David" (David McDermott), c. 1978; 154894 (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - "To Achieve Death", published in Fenris Wolf (Sweden), 1988; 156622 (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - "To the Best of Women", 1980; 154893 (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - "Techne-Theory", 1971-1974; 154892 (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - "The Vampire", undated; 154891 (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - "Vita Constrictor", 1983; 154890 (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - "The Voice of Candy", 1993; 154889 (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - X Magazine, copies of stories, 1977; 154887 (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Subseries B: Book-length Works, 154654
    - The Compleat Masochist: "Parts I and II, original", 1993; 156729 (Box 5, Folder 185 A)
    - The Compleat Masochist: Draft of "Editor's Foreward", undated; 156730 (Box 5, Folder 185 B)
    - The Compleat Masochist: Draft of "The Correct Masochist", undated; 156731 (Box 5, Folder 185 C)
    - The Compleat Masochist: Draft, undated; 156732 (Box 5, Folder 185 D)
    - The Compleat Masochist: "Parts I and II, rough draft for re-write", 1993; 156733 (Box 5, Folder 185 E)
    - The Compleat Masochist: original wrapper containing folders 185A through E, undated; 156737 (Box 5, Folder 185 F)
    - The Complete Masochist:Psychoanalytic Diary, 1993; 154744 (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - The Correct Sadist: "Semitexte: Polysexuality, Coprophagi and Urinology", undated; 154871 (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - The Correct Sadist: "Fragments, S&M Theme", undated; 154870 (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - The Correct Sadist: Journal, December through February, 1977-1978; 154869 (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - The Correct Sadist: "Early Angel Stern", various; 154868 (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - The Correct Sadist: "Angel Stern and Related Scraps", 1977; 154867 (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - The Correct Sadist: "Memoirs of Angel Stern", 1978; 154866 (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - The Correct Sadist: "S&M Dialogues", undated; 156625 (Box 5, Folder 192 A)
    - The Correct Sadist: "S&M, Raw Materials", various; 154865 (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - The Correct Sadist: "S&M Raw Material, Not Used", various; 154864 (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - The Correct Sadist: "Diary of Maitresse", undated; 154863 (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - The Correct Sadist: "Dominance Tricks Manuscripts", 1978; 154862 (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - The Correct Sadist: "The Cannibal Mouth", undated; 154861 (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - The Correct Sadist: Various Printed Materials, undated; 154860 (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - The Correct Sadist: Notes, William James and St. Augustine, undated; 154859 (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - The Correct Sadist: Notes, undated; 154858 (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part One, Originals, Roughs and Corrected Copies, undated; 154857 (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part I, Original, 1980; 154856 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part II, Roughs, and Originals, undated; 154855 (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part II, Originals and Rough Drafts, undated; 154854 (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part III, unused writings, 1970s; 154853 (Box 6, Folder 205)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part III, "The Beginning", undated; 154852 (Box 6, Folder 206)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part III, "Fatal", undated; 154851 (Box 6, Folder 207)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part III "The Threshold", 1979; 154850 (Box 6, Folder 208)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part III, final rough draft, undated; 154849 (Box 6, Folder 209)
    - The Correct Sadist, pages 1-22, undated; 154848 (Box 6, Folder 210)
    - The Correct Sadist, pages 23-52, undated; 154847 (Box 6, Folder 211)
    - The Correct Sadist, pages 53-79, undated; 154846 (Box 6, Folder 212)
    - The Correct Sadist, pages 53-79, undated; 154845 (Box 6, Folder 213)
    - The Correct Sadist, pages 80-109, undated; 154844 (Box 6, Folder 214)
    - The Correct Sadist, pages 140-164, undated; 154843 (Box 6, Folder 215)
    - The Correct Sadist, pages 165-189, undated; 154842 (Box 6, Folder 216)
    - The Correct Sadist: copy, pages 1-20, undated; 154841 (Box 6, Folder 217)
    - The Correct Sadist: copy, pages 21-45, undated; 154840 (Box 6, Folder 218)
    - The Correct Sadist: copy, pages 46-75, undated; 154839 (Box 6, Folder 219)
    - The Coreect Sadist: copy, pages 76-106, undated; 154838 (Box 6, Folder 220)
    - The Correct Sadist: second copy, pages 1-46, undated; 154837 (Box 6, Folder 221)
    - The Correct Sadist: Author's Forward, undated; 154836 (Box 6, Folder 222)
    - The Correct Sadist: Index, undated; 154835 (Box 6, Folder 223)
    - The Correct Sadist: revised manuscript, pages 1-30, 1981-1982; 154834 (Box 6, Folder 224)
    - The Correct Sadist: revised manuscript, pages 31-70, 1981-1982; 154833 (Box 6, Folder 225)
    - The Correct Sadist: revised manuscript, pages 71-106, 1981-1982; 154832 (Box 6, Folder 226)
    - The Correct Sadist: revised manuscript, pages 3-39, 1981-1982; 154831 (Box 6, Folder 227)
    - The Correct Sadist: revised manuscript, pages 1-40, 1981-1982; 154830 (Box 6, Folder 228)
    - The Correct Sadist: French Translation, "Dot Printing", undated; 154829 (Box 6, Folder 229)
    - The Correct Sadist: French Translation, "Laser Printing", undated; 154828 (Box 6, Folder 230)
    - The Correct Sadist: Appendix for U.K. publication, undated; 154827 (Box 6, Folder 231)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part I, Temple Press edition, undated; 154826 (Box 6, Folder 232)
    - The Correct Sadist: Part II, U.K. edition, undated; 154825 (Box 6, Folder 233)
    - The Correct Sadist: Temple Press Proof, 1989; 154824 (Box 6, Folder 234)
    - The Correct Sadist: Note on removed materials, 2002; 154823 (Box 6, Folder 235)
    - The Correct Sadist: Notes on uncorrected silvers pages 1-65, 1983; 154822 (Box 6, Folder 236)
    - The Correct Sadist: uncorrected silvers, pages 66-111, 1983; 154821 (Box 6, Folder 237)
    - The Correct Sadist: 'the last corrections' sent to Lanes, 1983; 154820 (Box 6, Folder 238)
    - The Correct Sadist: First Silver pages 1-163, 1983; 154819 (Box 6, Folder 239)
    - The Correct Sadist: Second Silver print, pages 1-163, 1983; 154818 (Box 6, Folder 240)
    - The Correct Sadist: The Third Silver, pages 11-159, 1983; 154817 (Box 6, Folder 241)
    - The Correct Sadist: printed from PDF, 2003; 154816 (Box 6, Folder 242)
    - The Correct Sadist: Mock-up, pages to scale, undated; 154815 (Box 6, Folder 243)
    - The Correct Sadist: Duplicate negatives of illustrations by Jeffrey Bretschneider, 1984; 154814 (Box 6, Folder 243 A)
    - The Correct Sadist: NY, Vitriol Publications, 1983; 154813 (Box 6, Folder 243 B)
    - The Correct Sadist: Specifications for Printers, undated; 154812 (Box 6, Folder 244)
    - The Correct Sadist: Production Costs, 1983; 154811 (Box 6, Folder 245)
    - The Correct Sadist: Postcards, undated; 154810 (Box 6, Folder 246)
    - The Correct Sadist: Promotional Materials, undated; 154809 (Box 6, Folder 247)
    - The Correct Sadist: Promotional Materials, undated; 154808 (Box 6, Folder 247 A)
    - The Correct Sadist: Promotional Postcards, undated; 154807 (Box 6, Folder 248)
    - The Correct Sadist: Ads and Press Materials, 1983-1996; 154806 (Box 6, Folder 249)
    - The Correct Sadist: Grove Street Press, 1983-1990; 154805 (Box 6, Folder 250)
    - The Correct Sadist: Grove Press Publication Party, 1985; 154804 (Box 6, Folder 251)
    - The Correct Sadist: Librarie Ernest Flammarion, 1984-1986; 154803 (Box 6, Folder 252)
    - The Correct Sadist: Blue Moon Contract, undated; 154802 (Box 6, Folder 253)
    - The Correct Sadist: Robert Merodack Contract (French publisher), 1988-1990; 154801 (Box 6, Folder 254)
    - The Correct Sadist: Italian Publishers, SHAKE, 1993-1997; 154800 (Box 6, Folder 255)
    - The Correct Sadist: Temple Books Contract (U.K. publisher), 1989; 154799 (Box 6, Folder 256)
    - The Correct Sadist: Press Notebook, undated; 154798 (Box 6, Folder 257)
    - The Correct Sadist: cover letters sent to publishers with manuscripts, c.1981; 154797 (Box 6, Folder 258)
    - The Correct Sadist: reviews, 1985; 154796 (Box 6, Folder 259)
    - The Correct Sadist:Lane Publications, 1984; 154795 (Box 6, Folder 260)
    - The Correct Sadist: Poster for reading, 1980; 154794 (Box 6, Folder 261)
    - The Correct Sadist:Times Square Show, 1980; 154793 (Box 6, Folder 261 A)
    - The Correct Sadist: Paris Readings, 1981; 154792 (Box 6, Folder 261 C)
    - The Correct Sadist:Reading at TR3, 1980; 154791 (Box 6, Folder 261 D)
    - The Correct Sadist:Postcard for Reading, undated; 154790 (Box 6, Folder 262)
    - The Correct Sadist: Blue Moon signing party invitation, 1996; 154789 (Box 6, Folder 262 A)
    - The Correct Sadist: Click and Drag Invitations, c.1995; 154788 (Box 6, Folder 262 B)
    - The Correct Sadist: Interview in The Face, 1983; 154787 (Box 7, Folder 263)
    - The Correct Sadist: Review in Screw Magazine, 1984; 154786 (Box 7, Folder 264)
    - The Correct Sadist: Review in East Village Eye, 1984; 154785 (Box 7, Folder 265)
    - The Correct Sadist: Reading, The Kitchen, 1981; 154784 (Box 7, Folder 266)
    - The Correct Sadist: Ratso Sloman Interview with Angel Stern, 1985; 154783 (Box 7, Folder 267)
    - The Correct Sadist: Soldes, 1979; 154782 (Box 7, Folder 268)
    - The Correct Sadist: Textuerre, Pose, 1981; 154781 (Box 7, Folder 269)
    - The Correct Sadist: Interview in High Times, 1985; 154780 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - The Correct Sadist: Harpers Excerpt (with unpublished editing), 1986; 154779 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - The Correct Sadist: L'Ennemi, Fag Rag, 1981; 154778 (Box 7, Folder 272)
    - The Correct Sadist II: Part I, 1996; 154777 (Box 7, Folder 273)
    - The Correct Sadist II: Part II, 1996; 154776 (Box 7, Folder 274)
    - The Correct Sadist II: Part II continued, 1996; 154775 (Box 7, Folder 275)
    - The Correct Sadist II: Part II continued, 1996; 154774 (Box 7, Folder 276)
    - The Correct Sadist II: Part III, 1996; 154773 (Box 7, Folder 277)
    - The Correct Sadist II: Dungeon Evidence, Velvet Publications, London, 1997; 154772 (Box 7, Folder 278)
    - The Correct Sadist: Dungeon Evidence, Manilla Envelope, undated; 154771 (Box 7, Folder 279)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: Diary, January through October, 1973; 154770 (Box 7, Folder 280)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: Journal February through July, 1973; 154769 (Box 7, Folder 281)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: Journal, September through December, 1973; 154768 (Box 7, Folder 282)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: Correspondence with George Coe aka Christopher Coe, author, 1972-73; 154767 (Box 7, Folder 283)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: background text, "The Dance", 1973; 154766 (Box 7, Folder 284)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: background text, "The Theory of Death", 1973; 154765 (Box 7, Folder 285)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: various printed materials, 1973; 154764 (Box 7, Folder 286)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: poems and short stories, 1973; 154763 (Box 7, Folder 287)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: background text, poems, 1973; 154762 (Box 7, Folder 288)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: scripts, 1973; 154761 (Box 7, Folder 289)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: background text, "Solitude", 1973; 154760 (Box 7, Folder 290)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: background text, "Zasu, Gelsomina", 1973; 154759 (Box 7, Folder 291)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: early draft, undated; 154758 (Box 7, Folder 292)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: early draft, undated; 154757 (Box 7, Folder 293)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: early draft, undated; 154756 (Box 7, Folder 294)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: first draft, 1994; 154755 (Box 7, Folder 295)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: first draft, 1994; 154754 (Box 7, Folder 296)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley, pages 1-25, 1995; 154753 (Box 7, Folder 297)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley, pages 26-50, 1995; 154752 (Box 7, Folder 298)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley, pages 51-75, 1995; 154751 (Box 7, Folder 299)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley, pages 76-102, 1995; 154750 (Box 7, Folder 300)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley, pages 1-25, 1973/2004; 154749 (Box 7, Folder 301)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley, pages 26-50, 1973/2004; 154748 (Box 7, Folder 302)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley, pages 51-75, 1973/2004; 154747 (Box 7, Folder 303)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley, pages 76-98, 1973/2004; 154746 (Box 7, Folder 304)
    - The Diary of Marie Stanley: manilla envelope, c.2004; 154745 (Box 7, Folder 305)
    - The Degenerate: research notes, undated; 154743 (Box 7, Folder 306)
    - The Degenerate: "The Birth of the Psyche", undated; 154742 (Box 7, Folder 307)
    - The Degenerate: printed materials, "Clinical Descriptions: Psychopath", various; 154741 (Box 7, Folder 308)
    - The Degenerate: notes from Crime and Punishment, undated; 154740 (Box 7, Folder 309)
    - The Degenerate: printed materials, excerpts from "Dementia Praecox", 1971; 154739 (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - The Degenerate: notes from "Sadism and Masochism" by Stekel, undated; 154738 (Box 7, Folder 311)
    - The Degenerate: notes from "Sadism and Masochism" by Stekel, continued, undated; 154737 (Box 7, Folder 312)
    - The Degenerate: various printed materials, "Schizophrenics-Speech", undated; 154736 (Box 7, Folder 313)
    - The Degenerate: new work, 1979; 154735 (Box 7, Folder 314)
    - The Degenerate: notes for "The Solitary", 1980; 154734 (Box 7, Folder 315)
    - The Degenerate: notes for "The Solitary", 1980; 154733 (Box 7, Folder 316)
    - The Degenerate: early draft, "The Solitary", 1979; 154732 (Box 7, Folder 317)
    - The Degenerate: "Aurora", unfinished story, undated; 154731 (Box 7, Folder 318)
    - The Degenerate: thematics, undated; 154730 (Box 7, Folder 319)
    - The Degenerate: "Cheri", undated; 154729 (Box 7, Folder 320)
    - The Degenerate: influences/Rainer/bibliography, undated; 154728 (Box 7, Folder 321)
    - The Degenerate: "Story of Rainer", 1979; 154727 (Box 7, Folder 322)
    - The Degenerate: Journal, Rainer, 1980; 154726 (Box 7, Folder 323)
    - The Degenerate: notes, drafts and various printed materials, undated; 154725 (Box 7, Folder 324)
    - The Degenerate: "Logic of the Elect", appendix, undated; 154724 (Box 7, Folder 325)
    - The Degenerate: rough drafts, undated; 154723 (Box 7, Folder 326)
    - The Degenerate: rough drafts, 1986; 154722 (Box 7, Folder 327)
    - The Degenerate: Part II, "Insanity", undated; 154721 (Box 7, Folder 328)
    - The Degenerate: Part II, "Philosophical", undated; 154720 (Box 8, Folder 329)
    - The Degenerate: Part III, "Corrections", 1987; 154719 (Box 8, Folder 330)
    - The Degenerate: Part II, "Robert in the Underworld", undated; 154718 (Box 8, Folder 331)
    - The Degenerate: "Robert in the Underworld" continued, undated; 154717 (Box 8, Folder 332)
    - The Degenerate: drafts and revisions, undated; 154716 (Box 8, Folder 333)
    - The Degenerate: drafts and revisions continued, undated; 154715 (Box 8, Folder 334)
    - The Degenerate:drats and notes, undated; 154714 (Box 8, Folder 335)
    - The Degenerate:Anne/Anne and Robert dialogs, her burgeoning masochism, undated; 154713 (Box 8, Folder 336)
    - The Degenerate: sections, undated; 154712 (Box 8, Folder 337)
    - The Degenerate: Robert's Diary, pg 120-449, undated; 154711 (Box 8, Folder 338)
    - The Degenerate: Robert's Diary, pg 453-480, undated; 154710 (Box 8, Folder 339)
    - The Degenerate: Part I, pages 1-19, 1991-1992; 154709 (Box 8, Folder 340)
    - The Degenerate: Part I, pages 20-41, 1991-1992; 154708 (Box 8, Folder 341)
    - The Degenerate:Part I, pages 42-63, 1991-1992; 154707 (Box 8, Folder 342)
    - The Degenerate:Part I, pages 64-87, 1991-1992; 154706 (Box 8, Folder 343)
    - The Degenerate: Part I, pages 88-105, 1991-1992; 154705 (Box 8, Folder 344)
    - The Degenerate:Part 1, pages 106-130, 1991-1992; 154704 (Box 8, Folder 345)
    - The Degenerate: Part I, pages 131-152, 1991-1992; 154703 (Box 8, Folder 346)
    - The Degenerate: Part I, pages 152-175b, 1991-1992; 154702 (Box 8, Folder 347)
    - The Degenerate: Part I, pages 176-200, 1991-1992; 154701 (Box 8, Folder 348)
    - The Degenerate: Part I, pages 201-216, 1991-1992; 154700 (Box 8, Folder 349)
    - The Degenerate: submission to agents and publishers, undated; 154699 (Box 8, Folder 350)
    - The Degenerate: Reading at Montreal, 1987; 154698 (Box 8, Folder 351)
    - The Degenerate: Published excerpts, Bomb and Vacation, 1982; 154697 (Box 8, Folder 352)
    - The Obsession: Draft, undated; 156635 (Box 8, Folder 352 A)
    - The Obsession: "Original and one copy", 1976; 156636 (Box 8, Folder 352 B)
    - The Obsession: I - draft, undated; 156637 (Box 8, Folder 352 C)
    - The Obsession: "Original, finished", 1977; 156638 (Box 8, Folder 352 D)
    - The Obsession: Final, correct copy pp.1-48, undated; 156639 (Box 8, Folder 352 E)
    - The Obsession: Final, correct copy pp.49-98, undated; 156640 (Box 8, Folder 352 F)
    - The Obsession: Final, correct copy pp.99-114, 3-35, undated; 156641 (Box 8, Folder 352 G)
    - The Obsession: Final, correct copy pp.41-78, undated; 156642 (Box 8, Folder 352 H)
    - The Obsession: Final, correct copy pp.79-117, undated; 156643 (Box 8, Folder 352 I)
    - The Obsession: II - original, 1977; 156644 (Box 8, Folder 352 J)
    - The Obsession: II - 2nd draft, 1978; 156646 (Box 8, Folder 352 K)
    - The Obsession: II - 2nd draft/Corrected, 1978; 156647 (Box 8, Folder 352 L)
    - The Obsession: II - original: final, 1979-80; 156648 (Box 8, Folder 352 M)
    - The Obsession: III - draft, undated; 156649 (Box 8, Folder 352 N)
    - The Obsession: Galleys, pieces of, undated; 156650 (Box 8, Folder 352 O)
    - The Obsession: Galleys, page 33-50, undated; 154696 (Box 8, Folder 353)
    - The Obsession: Galleys, page 51-65, undated; 154695 (Box 8, Folder 354)
    - The Obsession: Galleys page 66-80, undated; 154694 (Box 8, Folder 355)
    - The Obsession: Galleys, page 80-91, undated; 154693 (Box 8, Folder 356)
    - The Obsession: Boards, undated; 156670 (Box 8, Folder 356 A)
    - The Obsession: Boards, page 13-39, undated; 154692 (Box 8, Folder 357)
    - The Obsession: Boards, page 39-59, undated; 154691 (Box 8, Folder 358)
    - The Obsession: Boards, page 60-78, undated; 154690 (Box 8, Folder 359)
    - The Obsession: Boards, page 78-92, undated; 154689 (Box 8, Folder 360)
    - The Obsession: boards, page 93-109, undated; 154688 (Box 8, Folder 361)
    - The Obsession: Boards, page 111-117, undated; 154687 (Box 8, Folder 362)
    - The Obsession, softback edition, published by Vitriol Publications, etchings by Carl Apfelschnitt, 1986; 154686 (Box 8, Folder 362 A)
    - The Obsession: Promotional materials, 1986; 154685 (Box 8, Folder 362 B)
    - The Obsession: "Promotion Mailing", undated; 156659 (Box 8, Folder 362 C)
    - The Obsession: "Book Binding - Silk/Leather", undated; 156660 (Box 8, Folder 362 D)
    - The Obsession: "End papers", undated; 156661 (Box 8, Folder 362 E)
    - The Obsession: "Type styles, misdemeanors", undated; 156662 (Box 8, Folder 362 F)
    - The Obsession: Production estimates, undated; 156663 (Box 8, Folder 362 G)
    - The Obsession: Book production costs, undated; 156664 (Box 15, Folder 362 H)
    - The Obsession: "Money", undated; 156665 (Box 15, Folder 362 I)
    - The Obsession: Production schedule, undated; 156666 (Box 15, Folder 362 J)
    - The Obsession: original envelope with annotations, undated; 154684 (Box 15, Folder 363)
    - One Decadent Life: workbook, 1997; 154683 (Box 15, Folder 364)
    - One Decadent Life: Draft, Part III, undated; 154682 (Box 15, Folder 365)
    - One Decadent Life: diskette containing last chapters, 1998; 154681 (Box 15, Folder 366)
    - One Decadent Life: A Novel of Manhattan in 1985, pages 1-23, 1996-97; 154680 (Box 15, Folder 367)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 24-47, 1996-97; 154679 (Box 15, Folder 368)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 48-69, 1996-97; 154678 (Box 15, Folder 369)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 70-95, 1996-97; 154677 (Box 15, Folder 370)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 96-115, 1996-97; 154676 (Box 15, Folder 371)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 116-131, 1996-97; 154675 (Box 15, Folder 372)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 132-160, 1996-97; 154674 (Box 15, Folder 373)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 161-183, 1996-97; 154673 (Box 15, Folder 374)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 184-205, 1996-97; 154672 (Box 15, Folder 375)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 206-223, 1996-97; 154671 (Box 15, Folder 376)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 223-239, 1996-97; 154670 (Box 15, Folder 377)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 240-262, 1996-97; 154669 (Box 15, Folder 378)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 263-282, 1996-97; 154668 (Box 15, Folder 379)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 283-303, 1996-97; 154667 (Box 15, Folder 380)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 304-330, 1996-97; 154666 (Box 15, Folder 381)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 331-352, 1997-98; 154665 (Box 15, Folder 382)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 353-378, 1997-98; 154664 (Box 15, Folder 383)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 379-401, 1997-98; 154663 (Box 15, Folder 384)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 402-419, 1997-98; 154662 (Box 15, Folder 385)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 420-441, 1997-98; 154661 (Box 15, Folder 386)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 442-469, 1997-98; 154660 (Box 15, Folder 387)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 470-497, 1997-98; 154659 (Box 15, Folder 388)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 448-525, 1997-98; 154658 (Box 15, Folder 389)
    - One Decadent Life, "Journal of Transition", 1974; 154657 (Box 15, Folder 390)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 526-545, 1997-98; 154656 (Box 15, Folder 391)
    - One Decadent Life, pages 546-577, 1997-98; 154655 (Box 15, Folder 392)
  - Subseries C: Artwork for Terence Sellers' books, 154648
    - The Correct Sadist: pastel drawings by Jeffrey Bretschneider, undated; 154653 (Box 9, Folder 393)
    - Mistress Manslaughter: watercolor by Terence Sellers, undated; 154652 (Box 9, Folder 394)